Multidisciplinary Designer with over 7+ years of experience in marketing, brand and product design in various B2B and B2C channels for award-winning agencies, Fortune 500 companies, global enterprises, established businesses and startups globally launching successful campaigns, initiated branding initiatives, and developing digital products and design systems.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Creative Consultant at Glanbia 7

REMOTE | JUNE 2023 - PRESENT

Collaborated with key stakeholders and clients on the implementation and execution of lead-generation campaigns, providing tailored guidance and recommendations bespoke to their specific needs.

# Creative Developer at Glanbia

DUBLIN, IRELAND | SEPTEMBER 2022 - MAY 2023

Designed and executed digital marketing campaigns, rebranding and corporate refresh efforts, and developed key B2B collaterals and creative assets for Glanbia and Tirlán while exploring future technologies to drive future growth and innovation.

### Creative Associate at Glanbia

DUBLIN, IRELAND | FEBRUARY 2020 - AUGUST 2022

Collaborated with an award-winning cross-functional team to deliver successful B2B and B2C marketing and brand campaigns for 20+ brands in Glanbia's global portfolio, utilising diverse mediums such as AR, digital, print, motion, video, and interactive web experiences.

## Product Design Intern at Global Payments

DUBLIN, IRELAND | JULY 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

Contributed to Index, Global Payments' internal design system used by over 7000+ users worldwide, whilst conducting a UI audit for over 300+ products. Sole designer and researcher for Checkout Hero, a B2B product promoting eCommerce best practices, collaborating with multiple teams in an Agile environment.

### Freelance Graphic Designer at Lèngua

JAKARTA, INDONESIA | JULY 2017 - JUNE 2019

Executed successful social media marketing campaigns and branding initiatives in a 15+ member cross-functional team for over 30+ clients in diverse industries such as construction, healthcare, FMCG, F&B, banking, finance, fashion, and event management across Southeast Asia.

# Digital Media Associate at Dundalk BIDS7

DUNDALK, IRELAND | FEBRUARY 2018 - MARCH 2018

### Graphic Design Intern at SOE Jakarta <sup>¬</sup>

JAKARTA, INDONESIA | JULY 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

### Graphic Design Intern at alex[a]lexa

JAKARTA, INDONESIA | JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2015

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **UX Design Institute**

Professional Diploma in UX Design

DUBLIN, IRELAND | JANUARY 2023 - OCTOBER 2023

#### **Dundalk Institute of Technology**

First Class Honours

BA (Hons) Communications in Creative Media

DUNDALK, IRELAND | SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2019

#### SKILLS

#### Software

Adobe Creative Suite, Figma, Sketch, Miro, Mural InVision, HTML, CSS, JS, Framer, Wordpress, Spark AR, Ceros, Google Web Designer

#### Industry

Graphic design, branding & identity, motion graphics, illustrations, social media marketing, email marketing, print design, digital display advertising, augmented reality, UX research, UI design, design thinking, heuristic evaluation, competitive benchmarking, surveys, usability testing, user interviews, workshop facilitation, journey mapping, user flow, wireframing, prototyping, stakeholder relations, project management, training facilitation

# Languages

English - Native or bilingual Bahasa Indonesia - Native or bilingual

AWARDS & ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

# DesignOpp Creative Spotlight

DESIGNOPP | 2023

# DesignOpp Creative Directory

DESIGNOPP | 2023

## Best in Show via BLNKDISRUPTION

EXHIBITION - FÍS GRADUATE SHOW | 2019

## Types of Danger

EXHIBITION - KELLS TYPE TRAIL | 2019

## CERTIFICATIONS

### **Fundamentals of Digital Marketing**

G00GLE | 2022

# Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner

IBM | 2022

### Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)

TRIGRAPH INTELLIGENT LEARNING | 2022